<contentList>
<content contentuid="h6fea40e7gfd5fg4532g96fag91fe8800a15d">&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font size=1&gt;.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
<content contentuid="h877fb0a7g8985g4d26g9c97ge0c46599cb33">&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font size=1&gt;.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
<content contentuid="ha0eca831g2e16g463fgb80fg09f33092c2ee">&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font size=1&gt;.&lt;/font&gt;</content>
<content contentuid="h1bae56a9ga45fg431fg80bfg2afbef03c1d2">[1] restores Magic Armour after you recover from Frozen, Stunned, Petrified, Mad, Charmed, or Sleeping, and restores Physical Armour after Knocked Down or Chicken Form. Each point also adds 1 to your saving throws.</content>
<content contentuid="hded47ed1gcc2eg4ce8g9277g5ee6b7204293">[1] reflects received damage to your attacker. Each point also adds 1 to your status attempts.</content>
<content contentuid="h8256bf13gb4cag4662gaafegb5724b210c92">[1] grants Dodging and Resistance bonuses to all allies in a 5m radius. Affected allies also have a chance to gain advantage on any given saving throw, equal to 4% per point invested.</content>
<content contentuid="h5681c068g7150g4fb3gb552g1141b901f666">Bring it on. Combat is demanding, and your foes are devious and observant; for every surprise you spring, they will respond with two of their own. Not for the faint of heart!&lt;br&gt;With ABST, tactician bosses are granted advantage on all rolls. Other Tactician challenges can be enabled in the Fort Joy arena or the hold of the Lady Vengeance.</content>
<content contentuid="hf3cd8067g36c0g4b48ga4dfg361f33579b43">Reduces the cost of using grenades and scrolls by [2] AP.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking Ambidextrous also adds 5 to status attempts when your off-hand is free.</content>
<content contentuid="h6a4d6da0g29cfg44ecg8913g5a0a76cf1bbd">Gives you [2]% chance to recover a special arrow after shooting it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to your status attempt rolls with special arrows.</content>
<content contentuid="hc453e399ge1f5g41f1gaeabgcdd4de833c63">A character with [1] has an extra [2]% [3], but takes a [4]% penalty to [5]. Additionally, the maximum [3] is raised by [6]. Elemental casters must choose between the following:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Demon grants advantage to all status attempts made by your surfaces.&lt;br&gt;-Ice King adds a debuff effect to your Staff of Magus projectiles. Affected enemies will make their next save against a magic status with disadvantage.</content>
<content contentuid="h8ddc8dd4ge8feg4420ga6dag0d87ce8ec743">Lets you evade attacks of opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also grants advantage to your saves against surface-applied statuses.</content>
<content contentuid="h7a2f1a05g4b52g4ec2g8354g1f92a8bf442d">Shooting arrows will inflict bonus elemental damage depending on the surface your target is standing in.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Taking Elemental Ranger also grants advantage on weapon effect rolls made with bows and crossbows.</content>
<content contentuid="hcb8f9837gdf0fg4a01ga7d6g5ed522b74189">You can flee combat even when enemies are right next to you. Taking [1] also grants you the following situational bonuses:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Using Shields Up grants you advantage against the next hard disable (Stunned, Terrified, etc.) before the start of your next turn.&lt;br&gt;-Your Leadership aura grants allies a chance (4% per point invested) to make status attempt rolls with advantage.&lt;br&gt;-You make all saving throws with avantage when Flanked.</content>
<content contentuid="h98163163g695ag4813gb105g3ade9ea09050">[1] gives you [2] extra Action Points after dealing a killing blow.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Each kill also grants advantage to your next attempt that turn.</content>
<content contentuid="h6f77e8f2g044eg44a8gacb8g64457aac8c8f">Increases the range of skills and scrolls by [2]m. Does not affect melee and touch-range skills.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to weapon effect rolls made with ranged weapons and staves.</content>
<content contentuid="hd2ce8051g60adg4d7ega77cg86b745bd1b5c">[1] doubles the effects of food and potions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Eating food or drinking alcohol also grants advantage to your next saving throw; physical or magic, respectively.</content>
<content contentuid="hb6ef5200g4cd4g48dag8006gac3dc3e8aa51">Increases attack damage by [2]% while sneaking.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also grants advantage on status attempts made from sneaking or invisibility. This effect also triggers on your next attempt after starting a turn in smoke.</content>
<content contentuid="he94327f7g293dg488eg9d25gcb4f7ae7be24">Gives you an extra [2]% critical chance and [3]% more accuracy while you are at maximum Vitality.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 3 to status attempts when the same conditions are present.</content>
<content contentuid="h81ca938fg5ef4g452agb093g1294e2f0718b">[1] heals you when standing in blood.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Leeching blood also grants advantage to your next physical save or physical status attempt, whichever comes first.</content>
<content contentuid="h493986c9g104eg4517g9c49g90cee026cd6c">Adds [2]% of all healing you receive by skills or consumables to your Magic Armour.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to your magic saves and grants advantage on saves againt Necrofire.</content>
<content contentuid="hbde985cfgb1c4g4bb6g9a61gbec72c9b4ed6">Gives you [2] extra points in your Memory attribute.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also grants advantage on saves against Silenced or Disarmed.</content>
<content contentuid="h278b2bccg1afcg4314gbfcbgb10105ebc12b">When resurrected, you revive to full health.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Morning Person also grants advantage to your first save against a hard disable (Charmed, Petrified, etc.) per combat encounter. This effect resets on resurrection.</content>
<content contentuid="ha323378egb5f6g451cg858dged752a3540ca">Gives you the ability to perform attacks of opportunity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to weapon effect rolls made with bladed weapons and clubs.</content>
<content contentuid="h00f565c4g6178g424fgb031g41a2c12bf85d">You gain [2]% to Dodging while dual wielding.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also makes each attack you make or weapon skill you cast while dual wielding add 3 to status attempts rolls for the rest of your turn: melee weapons boost physical attempts, wands boost magic attempts.</content>
<content contentuid="h49426677g68f9g4467g947cg68fad9de4af8">Gives you +[2]% extra Vitality for every point in Warfare.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to your physical saves and grants advantage on saves against Decaying.</content>
<content contentuid="h90812fdfg4f53g49afg8a97g42aefdeb508c">Gives all magical skills a critical chance equal to your critical chance score.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also grants advantage to your attempts to Curse or drain Source from targets.</content>
<content contentuid="hfb8eec35g3339g4762g8382g712e74a2ac0b">You can throw grenades [2]m further. Taking [1] also grants you the following situational bonuses:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;-Your Flurry attacks make enemies roll with disadvantage on their next physical save.&lt;br&gt;-Your All-In attacks make enemies roll with disadvantage on their next status attempt.&lt;br&gt;-Your status attempts with grenades roll with +10 against enemies, -10 against allies.</content>
<content contentuid="hc37324bdg4088g4df7gbf3bg944c59d7eeb3">You explode upon death, dealing 50% of your vitality as physical damage in a 3 meter radius.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 5 to your status attempts rolls setting Blind, Crippled, Cursed, Dazed, Deaf, Decaying, Disarmed, Diseased, Infected, Nullified, Shackled, Silenced, Slowed, Taunted, and Weak, plus 5 for each of those statuses your target already has.</content>
<content contentuid="h6d76eb15gdb1ag4ebeg8001g58173516a923">Reduces all status durations by 1 turn, including positive statuses. Does not affect statuses with a duration of 1 turn.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Taking [1] also adds 3 to all your saving throws.</content>
<content contentuid="hd7c21999g602cg4497gaa65g41507b81eda1">[1] increases your recovery and maximum Action Points by [2] when your health is below [3]%.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Starting your turn below 50% health also grants advantage to your first status attempt that turn.</content>
</contentList>
